Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Manuscripts
  - Finding Aid (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Subseries 3: Traveling Exhibitions
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Ragone, Keith (Folder 2 of 2), February - April, 1997, 114 leaves (Box-folder 13/196)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Hebrew, Ukrainian and Yiddish.
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Flyers and Posters, February - April, 1997, 40 leaves (Box-folder 13/197)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Photographs, February-April, 1997, 7 leaves (128 color prints, 24 negative strips) (Box-folder 13/198)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Opening Photographs, February - April, 1997, 4 leaves (10 black and white prints) (Box-folder 14/199)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Slides, February - April, 1997, 1 leaf (14 slides) (Box-folder 14/200)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Press Kit, February - April, 1997, 21 leaves (Box-folder 14/201)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Press, February - April, 1997, 68 leaves (Box-folder 14/202)
      - The Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Comment Book, February - April, 45 leaves (Box-folder 14/203)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel, Various Documents, July-March, 141 leaves (Box-folder 14/204)
        The manuscript materials are in English, German, Hebrew, Yiddish and Russian.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Research (Folder 1 of 2), July-March, 1997-1998, 67 leaves (Box-folder 14/205)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Hebrew and Yiddish.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Research (Folder 2 of 2), July, 1997-1998, 1 leaf (49 color prints) (Box-folder 14/206)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Simon Wiesenthal Center Museum of Tolerance, July-March, 1997-1998, 16 leaves (Box-folder 14/207)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Testimonies (Folder 1 of 2), July-March, 1997-1998, 124 leaves (Box-folder 14/208)
        The manuscript materials are in Hebrew, Yiddish, Russian and Ukrainian.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Testimonies (Folder 2 of 2), July-March, 1997-1998, 146 leaves (Box-folder 14/209)
        The manuscript materials are in Hebrew, Yiddish, and Russian.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Testimonies Translations, July-March, 1997-1998, 89 leaves (Box-folder 15/210)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Packet Sent, 1997-1998, 160 leaves (Box-folder 15/211)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Administrative (Folder 1 of 3), 1997-1998, 138 leaves (Box-folder 15/212)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Administrative (Folder 2 of 3), 1997-1998, 100 leaves (Box-folder 15/213)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Administrative (Folder 3 of 3), 1997-1998, 96 leaves (Box-folder 15/214)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation (Folder 1 of 3), 1997-1998, 139 leaves (Box-folder 15/215)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Hebrew, German, Yiddish, Russian and Polish.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation (Folder 2 of 3), 1997-1998, 98 leaves (Box-folder 15/216)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation (Folder 3 of 3), 1997-1998, (11 color prints) (Box-folder 15/217)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Print Photocopies, 1997-1998, 70 leaves (Box-folder 16/218)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation Photographs (Folder 1 of 2), 1997-1998, 1 leaf (70 color prints, 10 negative strips) (Box-folder 16/219)
        The manuscript material is in English.
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation Photographs (Folder 2 of 2), 1997-1998, 1 leaf (52 color prints, 7 negative strips) (Box-folder 16/220)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Installation Slides, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 16/221)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Invitation and Brochure, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 16/222)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Press, 1997-1998, 57 leaves (Box-folder 16/223)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Opening, 1997-1998, 6 leaves (1 color print) (Box-folder 16/224)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Catalogs, 1997-1998, 20 leaves (Box-folder 16/225)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Checklist and Numbered Catalog, 1997-1998, 44 leaves (Box-folder 16/226)
      - Yeshiva University Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Design, 1997-1998, 56 leaves (Box-folder 16/227)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Vinyl Letters, 1997-1998, 35 leaves (Box-folder 16/228)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Artifact List, 1997-1998, 8 leaves (Box-folder 16/229)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Quotes, 1997-1998, 106 leaves (Box-folder 16/230)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Maps, 1997-1998, 38 leaves (Box-folder 16/231)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Captions, Traveling Exhibitions, September -January, 1997-1998, 96 leaves (Box-folder 16/232)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Captions, 1997-1998, 1 leaf (Box-folder 17/233)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY Administrative, September - January, 1997-1998, 108 leaves (Box-folder 17/234)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Slides, September - January, 1997-1998, 12 leaves (108 color slides) (Box-folder 17/235)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Brochure, September - January, 1997-1998, 70 leaves (Box-folder 17/236)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Invitation, September - January, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17/237)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Flyer Distribution, September - January, 1997-1998, 96 leaves (Box-folder 17/238)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Ruth Messinger's Proclamation, September - January, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17/239)
        See oversized box: 1/12
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Group Visits, September - January, 1997-1998, 25 leaves (Box-folder 17/240)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Press, September - January, 1997-1998, 81 leaves (Box-folder 17/241)
      - Yeshiva University Museum Dinner Honoring Aaron Ziegelman, September, 1997-1998, 100 leaves (Box-folder 17/242)
      - The Atkinson Museum, Hampden - Sydney College, Hampden-Sydney, VA - Administrative, March - May, 1997, 52 leaves (Box-folder 17/243)
      - The Atkinson Museum, Hampden - Sydney College, Hampden-Sydney, VA - Installation, March - May, 1998, 15 leaves (29 color prints, 7 negative strips) (Box-folder 17/244)
      - The Jewish Community Center, Minneapolis, MN - Administrative, September - October, 1998, 60 leaves (Box-folder 18/245)
      - Rotunda of the Russell Senate Building, Washington, DC - Photographs (Folder 1 of 2), October, 1999, 3 leaves (44 color prints) (Box-folder 18/246)
      - Rotunda of the Russell Senate Building, Washington, DC - Photographs (Folder 2 of 2), October, 1999, 2 leaves (58 color prints) (Box-folder 18/247)
      - Sanford L. Ziff Jewish Museum of Florida, Miami, FL - Education Program, February, 1999, 55 leaves (Box-folder 18/248)
      - Makor, New York, NY - Administrative, June - August, 2000, 28 leaves (Box-folder 18/249)
      - Long Beach Jewish Community Center, Long Beach, CA - Administrative, 2000, 50 leaves (Box-folder 18/250)
      - The Jewish Historical Institute, Warsaw, Poland - Administrative, November-February, September - October, 2000, 18 leaves (Box-folder 18/251)
      - Schatten Gallery, Emory University, Atlanta, GA - Administrative, 2001-2002, 29 leaves (Box-folder 18/252)
      - Luboml II - Administrative (Folder 1 of 2), March - May, 2002, 116 leaves (Box-folder 18/253)
      - Luboml II - Administrative (Folder 2 of 2), 1996-2002, 125 leaves (Box-folder 18/254)
      - Luboml II - List of Photographs, 1996-2002, 33 leaves (Box-folder 18/255)
      - Luboml II, West End Synagogue, New York, NY - Administrative, March - April, 1996-2002, 87 leaves (Box-folder 18/256)
      - Luboml II, West End Synagogue, New york, NY - Invitation, March - April, 1996, 37 leaves (Box-folder 18/257)
      - Luboml II, West End Synagogue, New York, NY - Comment Book, March - April, 1996, 50 leaves (Box-folder 18/258)
      - Luboml II, Hebrew Home for the Aged, Riverdale, NY - Administrative, January - February, 1996, 1 leaf (Box-folder 19/259)
      - Luboml II, Temple Israel of Long Beach, Long Beach, NY - Administrative, June - August, 1998, 12 leaves (Box-folder 19/260)
      - Luboml II, Katz Jewish Community Center, Cherry Hill, NJ - Administrative, March, 1999, 13 leaves (Box-folder 19/261)
      - Luboml II, Smith College Hillel, Northampton, MA - Administrative, April - May, 2000, 15 leaves (Box-folder 19/262)
      - Luboml II, Holocaust Museum and Learning Center, St. Louis, MO - Administrative, January - February, 2000, 17 leaves (Box-folder 19/263)
      - Luboml II, The Holocaust Center, Pittsburgh, PA - Administrative, October - November, 2001, 19 leaves (Box-folder 19/264)
    - Subseries 4: Publicity
      - Press Contacts, 1996, 30 leaves (Box-folder 19/265)
      - Personal Contacts, 1997-2001, 44 leaves (Box-folder 19/266)
      - Luboml Exhibition Project Brochure, 1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 19/267)
        See oversize box: 2/19
      - Libivners E-mails, 1997, 76 leaves (Box-folder 19/268)
      - Berenbaum Letter (Master), 1997-1999, 8 leaves (Box-folder 19/269)
      - National Yiddish Book Center, 1997, 27 leaves (Box-folder 19/270)
      - The Holocaust Chronicle Publicity Kit, 1997, 44 leaves (Box-folder 19/271)
      - Quotations for the Exhibit, 2000, 25 leaves (Box-folder 19/272)
      - Flattering Notes, Undated, 26 leaves (Box-folder 19/273)
      - Exhibition Insurance, 1997-1998, 3 leaves (Box-folder 19/274)
      - Articles on Polish Shtetls, 1998, 6 leaves (Box-folder 19/275)
      - Luboml Museum Donation, 1994, 1998, 57 leaves (Box-folder 19/276)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Russian and Ukraine.
      - "A Shtetl Called Luboml" - A child's story by Gloria Goldreich with Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-1997, 6 leaves (Box-folder 19/277)
      - "The Tragedy of Fall 1942" by Mikola Dzei. English Translation, September 19, Undated, 24 leaves (Box-folder 19/278)
      - Aaron Ziegelman's Biography, 1998, 4 leaves (Box-folder 19/279)
      - Appraisals, 1997, 23 leaves (Box-folder 19/280)
      - Mailing Lists - Masters, 1997, 87 leaves (Box-folder 19/281)
      - Luboml - Addresses often needed, Undated, 26 leaves (Box-folder 19/282)
      - Article List, August 8, 1999, 7 leaves (Box-folder 20/283)
      - Packet - Master Articles, 1997, 106 leaves (17 color transparency) (Box-folder 20/284)
      - Luboml Mini-Exhibit Instructions - Insurance Samples, 1997-1998, 59 leaves (Box-folder 20/285)
      - Vice President Al Gore, Letter, 1996, 3 leaves (Box-folder 20/286)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Invitation, 1999, 7 leaves (Box-folder 20/287)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Artifact Labels, 1997, 1 leaf 14 board-mounted artifact labels (Box-folder 20/288)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Color Photocopies of Exhibitions, 1997, 3 leaves (Box-folder 20/289)
        See oversize box: 2/29
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Philadelphia Inquirer, April 9, 1997, 4 leaves (Box-folder 20/290)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Jewish Exponent, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 20/291)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Courier - Post, March 19, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 20/292)
      - Gershman Y, Philadelphia, PA - Comment Book Selections, April, 1997, 27 leaves (Box-folder 20/293)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Comments, 1997, 29 leaves (Box-folder 20/294)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - The Jerusalem Report, July 24, 1997-1998, 3 leaves (Box-folder 20/295)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - The Jerusalem Post, June 29, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 20/296)
      - Yad Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel - Jerusalem Post Magazine, July 11, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 20/297)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Press Contacts, 1997, 30 leaves (Box-folder 20/298)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Text, 1997, 53 leaves (Box-folder 20/299)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Credit Panel, Comment Cards, 1997, 20 leaves (Box-folder 20/300)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Artifacts, 1997, 147 leaves (Box-folder 20/301)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Spanish, Yiddish, German Russian, Ukrainian and Hebrew.
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Extra Photos, 1997, 59 leaves (Box-folder 20/302)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Russian and Hebrew.
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Quote Panels, 1997, 27 leaves (Box-folder 20/303)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Opening Event, April 10, 1997, (9 contact sheets) (Box-folder 20/304)
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Comment Book, 1997, 114 leaves (Box-folder 20/305)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Polish, Russian and Hebrew.
      - Yeshiva University, Cardozo School of Law, New York, NY - Press Clippings, 1997-1999, 18 leaves (Box-folder 20/306)
        Additional oversize materials can be found in oversize box: 2/20-22
      - The Atkinson Museum, Hampden-Sydney College, Hampden-Sydney, VA - Installation, 1997, 67 leaves (Box-folder 21/307)
      - The Atkinson Museum, Hampden-Sydney College, Hampden-Sydney, VA - Press Clippings, 1998, 51 leaves (Box-folder 21/308)
      - The War Memorial Museum, Newport News, VA - Installation, 1998, 24 leaves (Box-folder 21/309)
      - The Jewish Museum of Western Canada, Winnipeg, Manitoba - Poster and Invitation, 1998, 13 leaves (Box-folder 21/310)
      - The Jewish Museum of Western Canada, Winnipeg, Manitoba - Customs, 1997-1998, 4 leaves (Box-folder 21/311)
      - The Jewish Museum of Western Canada, Winnipeg, Manitoba - Program, 1998, 11 leaves (Box-folder 21/312)
      - The Jewish Museum of Maryland, Baltimore, MD - Press Release, 1997-1998, 17 leaves (Box-folder 21/313)
      - Montreal Holocause Memorial Centre, Montreal, Quebec - Exhibition, 1997-1999, 29 leaves (Box-folder 21/314)
      - Rotunda of the Russell Senate Building, Washington, DC - Installation, 1999, 97 leaves (Box-folder 21/315)
      - Rotunda of the Russell Senate Building, Washington, DC - Correspondence, 1999, 36 leaves (Box-folder 21/316)
      - Sanford L. Ziff Jewish Museum of Florida, Miami, FL - Invitation and Booklet, 1999, 27 leaves (Box-folder 21/317)
      - Sanfrod L. Ziff Jewish Museum of Florida, Miami, FL - Press Clippings, 1999-2000, 23 leaves (Box-folder 21/318)
      - Boston Public Library, Boston, MA -Installation, 2000, 11 leaves (Box-folder 21/319)
      - Tennessee Venues - Program, 1999-2000, 7 leaves (Box-folder 21/320)
      - The Jewish Museum Camden Town, London, England - Flyers and Posters, 1995, 43 leaves (Box-folder 21/321)
      - the Jewish Museum Camden Town, London, England - Press clippings, 2001, 18 leaves (Box-folder 21/322)
      - The Jewish Historical Institute, Warsaw, Poland - Press clippings, 2001, 11 leaves (Box-folder 21/323)
      - Hebrew Home for the Aged, Riverdale, NY - Press clippings, Undated, 6 leaves (Box-folder 21/324)
      - Plainview Old Bethpage John F Kennedy High School, Plainview, NY - Correspondence, 1997-1998, 6 leaves (Box-folder 21/325)
      - The Museum of Anthropology, University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC - Installation, 1997-1998, 64 leaves (6 color prints) (Box-folder 21/326)
      - The Jewish Community Center, Richmond, VA - Press clippings, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 22/327)
      - The Jewish Community Center, Richmond, VA - Press clippings, 1999 (Box-folder 22/328)
      - The Jewish Community Center, Richmond, VA - Teacher's Guide, 1999, 12 leaves (Box-folder 22/329)
      - Brandeis, Waltham, MA - Installation, Undated, 5 leaves (Box-folder 22/330)
      - Bates College, Lewiston, ME - Installation, Publicity, 1999, 36 leaves (9 color prints) (Box-folder 22/331)
      - Temple Israel of Long Beach, Long Beach, NY - Installation, 1998-1999, 4 leaves (Box-folder 22/332)
      - Temple Beth-El of Great Neck, Great Neck, NY - Installation, 1999, 14 leaves (Box-folder 22/333)
      - Center for Russia, East Europe, and Central Asia, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI - Installation, 1999, 21 leaves (Box-folder 22/334)
      - Reconstructionist Rabbinical college, Wyncote, PA - Installation, 1999, 10 leaves (Box-folder 22/335)
      - Fondren Main Library, Rice University, Houston, TX - Installation, 2000, 7 leaves (Box-folder 22/336)
      - Luboml III - Captions, 2000-2001, 9 leaves (Box-folder 22/337)
      - The Jewish Week, July 26, 2000, 9 leaves (Box-folder 22/338)
      - The Jewish Week, April 8, 1985, 2 leaves (Box-folder 22/339)
      - The Jewish Week, November 22-28, 1991, 5 leaves (Box-folder 22/340)
      - Sh'ma: A Journal of Jewish Responsibility, April 14, 1995, 8 leaves (Box-folder 22/341)
      - Yedi’ot Aharonot, August 18, 1995, 37 leaves (Box-folder 22/342)
        The manuscript materials are in Hebrew with English translation.
      - The Jewish Week, September 1, 1995, 7 leaves (Box-folder 22/343)
      - The Jewish Week, October 13, 1995, 13 leaves (Box-folder 22/344)
        See oversize box: 1/4
      - The Jewish Journal of Greater Los Angeles, November 3-9, 1995, 4 leaves (Box-folder 22/345)
      - Forward, December 15, 1995, 4 leaves (Box-folder 22/346)
        See oversize box: 1/1
      - Our Life, January 6, 1995, 7 leaves (Box-folder 22/347)
        The manuscript materials are in Ukrainian.
      - Manhattan Spirit, March 22, 1996, 3 leaves (Box-folder 22/348)
      - The New York Times, March 20, 1996, 7 leaves (Box-folder 22/349)
      - Jewish Exponent, April 11, 1996, 7 leaves (Box-folder 22/350)
        See oversize box: 1/5
      - International Jewish News, July 11, 1996, 1 leaf (Box-folder 22/351)
      - The Jerusalem Post Magazine, July 11, 1997, 10 leaves (Box-folder 22/352)
      - The Rhode Island Jewish Herald, July 10, 1997, 1 leaf. (Box-folder 22/353)
      - Yedioth Achronoth, July 1, 1997, 16 leaves (Box-folder 22/354)
      - Jerusalem Yad Vashem, Summer, 1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 22/355)
      - The Jerusalem Post, June 29, 1997, 6 leaves (Box-folder 22/356)
      - The Jewish Week, Mary 2, 1997, 6 leaves (Box-folder 22/357)
      - Voice, March 26, 1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 22/358)
      - Jewish Exponent, March 13, 1997, 3 leaves (Box-folder 22/359)
      - Courier-Post, March 9, 1997, 1 leaf (Box-folder 22/360)
      - Jewish Exponent, February 27, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 22/361)
      - Lilith, Winter, 1997, 26 leaves (Box-folder 22/362)
      - The New York Times Magazine, December 22, 1997-1998, 2 leaves (Box-folder 22/363)
      - Moment, December, 1996, 5 leaves (Box-folder 22/364)
      - Long Island Jewish Week, September 27, 1996, 1 leaf (Box-folder 22/365)
      - The Jerusalem Report, July 24, 1996, 8 leaves (Box-folder 23/366)
      - The Jewish Week, Publicty, August 8, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 23/367)
      - Hadassah Magazine, August-September, 1997, 20 leaves (Box-folder 23/368)
      - Image, September, 1997, 3 leaves (Box-folder 23/369)
      - Fire Island News, August 29-September 4, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 23/370)
      - The New York Times, September 21, 1997, 4 leaves (Box-folder 23/371)
      - Daily News, October 2, 1997, 6 leaves (Box-folder 23/372)
      - The Jewish Week, October 24, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 23/373)
      - Congressional Record, November 7, 1997, 2 leaves (Box-folder 23/374)
      - ThisWeek, November 19, 1997, 18 leaves (Box-folder 23/375)
      - Forward, November 21, 1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 23/376)
      - Congress Monthly, November-December, 1997, 8 leaves (Box-folder 23/377)
      - Lifestyles, New Year, 1997, 9 leaves (Box-folder 23/378)
      - Manhattan Spirit, January 15, 1998, 5 leaves (Box-folder 23/379)
      - The Farmville (VA) Herald, February 25, 1998, 5 leaves (Box-folder 23/380)
      - Richmond Times Dispatch, March 1, 1998, 3 leaves (Box-folder 23/381)
      - The News and Advance, March 8, 1998, 5 leaves (Box-folder 23/382)
      - The Farmville Herald, March 11, 1998, 12 leaves (Box-folder 23/383)
      - The Correspondent Virginia War Museum, Summer, 1998, 2 leaves (Box-folder 23/384)
      - The Virginian-Pilot, June 29, 1998, 14 leaves (Box-folder 23/385)
      - Newseum, September, 1998, 4 leaves (Box-folder 23/386)
      - The Sophian, April 27, 1998, 1 leaf (Box-folder 23/387)
      - The New York Times, April 29, 2000, 3 leaves (Box-folder 23/388)
      - Library of Congress Public Relations Material, 2008, 21 leaves (Box-folder 23/389)
      - Fanya Gottesfeld Heller - Publicity Kit, 2002-2003, 297 leaves (Box-folder 23/390)
    - Subseries 5: Luboml Memorial Book
      - Yizkor Book Publication, 1996, 125 leaves (Box-folder 24/391)
        The manuscript materials are in English, Yiddish (illegible) and Hebrew.
      - The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl, November 26 (1 of 3), 1996, 76 leaves (Box-folder 24/392)
      - The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl, November 26 (2 of 3), 1996, 68 leaves (Box-folder 24/393)
      - The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl, November 26 (3 of 3), 1996, 80 leaves (Box-folder 24/394)
        See oversize box 1/8
      - Yizkor Book Publication, 1996, 123 leaves (Box-folder 24/395)
      - Yizkor Book Publication, Corrections, March 5, 1996-1997, 49 leaves (Box-folder 24/396)
        The manuscript materials are in English and Yiddish (illegible).
      - Yizkor Book Publication - Administrative (1 of 2), 1997, 145 leaves (Box-folder 24/397)
      - Yizkor Book Publication - Administrative (2 of 2), 1996-1997, 171 leaves (Box-folder 24/398)
        Additional materials can be found in oversize box: 1/7
      - KTAV's Copy Editor's Edit, June 20 (1 of 3), 1996-1997, 150 leaves (Box-folder 25/399)
      - KTAV's Copy Editor's Edit, June 20 (2 of 3), 1996, 130 leaves (Box-folder 25/400)
      - KTAV's Copy Editor's Ediot, June 20 (3 of 3), 1996, 143 leaves (Box-folder 25/401)
      - Danny Soyer's Corrections (1 of 3), 1996, 175 leaves (Box-folder 25/402)
      - Danny Soyer's Corrections (2 of 3), 127 leaves (Box-folder 25/403)
      - Danny Soyer's Corrections (3 of 3), 86 leaves (Box-folder 25/404)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yizkor Book (1 of 3), 145 leaves (Box-folder 26/405)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yizkor Book (2 of 3), 1996, 129 leaves (Box-folder 26/406)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yizkor Book (3 of 3), 1996, 151 leaves (Box-folder 26/407)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yitzkor [sic] Book with Notes (1 of 2), 1996, 193 leaves (Box-folder 26/408)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yitzkor Book [sic] with Notes (2 of 2), 197 leaves (Box-folder 26/409)
      - Pinkas Luboml - Libivner Yizkor Book - Bound Version, 395 leaves (Box-folder 27/410)
      - Yizkor Book of Luboml - Hebrew Version, 204 leaves (Box-folder 27/411)
        The manuscript materials are in Hebrew and English.
      - Permissions, 33 leaves (Box-folder 27/412)
      - Yizkor Book Order Forms, 1996, 6 leaves (Box-folder 27/413)
      - Press and Reactions, 23 leaves (Box-folder 27/414)
      - Yizkor Book Erata, 1997, 5 leaves (Box-folder 27/415)
      - KTAV Review Copy of Luboml: The Memorial Book of a Vanished Shtetl, June 10, 1997, 224 leaves (Box-folder 27/416)